# KEIRY HERNANDEZ BEATRIZ

# **BUILDING DESIGNER**

# **CONTACT INFORMATION**



(631) 220-2070



khbeatriz@gmail.com



41-01 67th ST, Woodside New York 11377

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Degree in Architecture

New York Institute of Technology, Old Westbury 2010 - 2017

# **SKILLS**

Efficient in the following programs:

- Adobe In-Design
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Autocad
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Word
- Revit
- Rhinoceros

#### OTHER:

- Army Reservist (Current) US Army Corps of Engineers
- Bilingual English & Spanish

### **PROFILE**

Experienced for a total of eight (8) years. With five (5) of those years being in residential and three (3) being in schools, Pharmaceutical, and State projects. Responsibilities often included design enhancement, coordination, and integration of utilities systems within buildings. As well as filing Building Permits in different munincipalities.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Junior Level - Building Designer** Stantec

March 2018 - Current

Working within a network of different disciplines, has allowed to gain a broader knowledge of what each one does. This has given the ability to understand and work efficiently on Architectural Sets.

## Pfizer Warehouse Addition

Assisted with the addition of designing a warehouse of 390 pallet storage. The program requirements were open office, freezer/refrigeration, hazardous material area, and quarantine rejects. Floor plans and elevations were required.

# School Construction Authority

For this particular school, interior and exterior work needed to be done. Generated floor plans, sections, details, and elevations in autocad. The exterior ramp had to be updated to code.

#### Regeneron

Assisted with construction documents. The client wanted to renovate an existing part of the building to meet the standards of new lab work. Multiple scientists had different wants and needs for their 40+ labs. On top of design work, constant track of 300+ old and new equipments to each designated area and functionality.

## **Entry Level - Drafting Design Eduardo Lacroze Architecture**

**July 2017 - March 2018** 

The residential firm main focus was on high end residents. Had the opportunity to work closely among the clients, as well as with general contractors. Worked with the other office located in Argentina to design renderings.

### ■ Turilli Residence

Lead building design/construction documents on renovating and expanding the kitchen, family room, and mudhall. The house was a two story frame dwelling home.

# **Intern Level - Draftsman Andreas Letkovsky Architecture P.C**

September 2013 - 2017

The residential firm worked on small projects. Majority of it was interior renovation. Worked with multiple building departments to file building permits.

#### Cliette Residence

Lead building designer and coordinated construction documents. The client needed a new septic system and retaining wall. A topographic cross section had to be generated to show location of system and wall. Alongside this, a radius map had to be drawn out for the Suffolk Waste Water Management.